{
    "subject": "resource/Rodney_Robert_Porter",
    "predicate": "ontology/doctoralAdvisor",
    "object": "resource/Frederick_Sanger",
    "human_readable": "Rodney Robert Porter's doctoral advisor was Frederick Sanger.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9351497292518616,
            "question": "Who was Rodney Robert Porter's doctoral advisor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9128902554512024,
            "question": "Frederick Sanger played what role in Rodney Robert Porter's academic journey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8855413198471069,
            "question": "Name the advisor of Rodney Robert Porter."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8643234968185425,
            "question": "What field of study did Rodney Robert Porter and Frederick Sanger likely work in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8148507475852966,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Rodney Robert Porter and Frederick Sanger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7891137003898621,
            "question": "Can you describe the connection between Rodney Robert Porter and Frederick Sanger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7546225786209106,
            "question": "Who guided Rodney Robert Porter during his doctoral studies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5924811363220215,
            "question": "What is the name of the scientist who advised Rodney Robert Porter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5048336982727051,
            "question": "Frederick Sanger is known for what contribution to science?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5027939081192017,
            "question": "Who mentored Rodney Robert Porter during his doctoral research?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rodney Robert Porter's doctoral advisor was Frederick Sanger.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7845_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Frederick Sanger is known for what contribution to science?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7845_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the scientist who advised Rodney Robert Porter?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7845_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who guided Rodney Robert Porter during his doctoral studies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7845_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7845_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7845_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7845_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7845_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7845_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7845_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7845_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7845_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7845_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7845_43.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can confirm that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe text mentions that Rodney Robert Porter's supervisor during his PhD (awarded in 1948) was Frederick Sanger. Additionally, another document mentions that Porter had been the first doctoral student of Frederick Sanger, further solidifying this relationship."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Rodney Robert Porter was Frederick Sanger's first doctoral student, supporting the statement that Frederick Sanger was Rodney Robert Porter\u2019s doctoral advisor."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}